Guide to the Ronald Lawson Research Files for the Tenant Movement in New York City TAM.214
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Research Files (box 6): Leadership Questionnaires: Neighborhood Organizations
  - Eighth Avenue Tenants League for Senior Citizens: Lillian Reeves (043-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Eldridge Community Center: Marcelio Rosario (044-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Flatbush Tenants Council: Marty Markowitz (045-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Flatbush Tenants Council: Rosetta Shore (045-02), undated (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Fordham Bedford Coalition: Bill Fischer (046-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - F.D.R. Independent Democratic Club Rent Clinic: Ruth Silverman (047-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - F.D.R. Independent Democratic Club Rent Clinic: Jack Deutsch (047-02), undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Fresh Meadows Tenant Association: David Buckwalter (049-01), undated (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Fresh Meadows Tenant Association: Lionel Sapinkopf, undated (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Research Files (box 7): Leadership Questionnaires: Neighborhood Organizations
  - Glen Oaks Tenant Association: Al Brooks (050-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Tenants Union: Herbert Williams (051-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Henry Street Settlement: Larry Levner (052-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Henry Street Settlement: Ora Dorsey (052-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Housing Conservation Co-ordinators: Gloria Milliken (054-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Housing Conservation Co-ordinators: Pat Cunningham (054-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Hudson Guild Service Center: Frank Strock (055-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ingersoll-Willoughby Housing Center: Mr. Swann (056-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Inwood Tenant Association: J. Quirk (057-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - It's Time: Amparo Tirado (058-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - It's Time: Selita Cabrera (058-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Kelly Street Block Association: Esther Hazel (059-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Knightsbridge Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association: Ralph Menendez (060-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Knightsbridge Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association: Patricia Burns (060-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - La Casa: J. Pahiagua (062-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - League of Autonomous Bronx Organization for Renewal: Marshal England (061-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association: Barbara Chocky (063-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Association of Tenants of Lincoln Towers: Shirley Quill (065-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln Towers Tenants Association: Bernard Krebs (065-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Longwood Community Management: Ely Colon (066-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Los Sures: Jim Harris (067-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Los Sures: Henry Lanier (067-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Los Sures: Larry Al Garhey (067-03), undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Lower East Side Community Corp.: Ms. G. Gambaro (068-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Manhattan Valley Development Corp.: Jose Acuna (069-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Marble Kingsbridge Futures Association: Jim Vogt (070-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Marble Kingsbridge Futures Association: Sarah Gay (070-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Melrose Organization: Robit Muniz (071-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Metropolitan Avenue Tenants Association: Iris Vargas (072-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Met Council: Jane Benedict (073-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Met Council: Howard Scheeter (073-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Met Council: David Surrey (073-03), undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Met Council Bay Ridge Branch: George Alwon (074-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Met Council Bronx Branch: Joe Hyler (075-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Met Council Crown Heights Branch: Sue Cohen (076-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Met Council Harlem Branch: Bess Stevenson (077-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Middle Income Residents Association: Charles Loome (140-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Mitchell-Lama Council: Jim Garst (080-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Mitchell-Lama and Allied Housing Inc. (Brooklyn): Norman Lazarus (081-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Morris Heights Neighborhood Association: Roger Hayes (082-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Morris Heights Neighborhood Improvement Association: Nilda Occassio (082-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Mosholv/Woodlawn Square Community Coalition: Peter Bourbeau (083-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Neighborhood Board 3, Inc: Mr. C. Miles (084-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Neighborhood Board 3, Inc.: Arthur Brown (084-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Neighborhood Board 5: K. Hunt (085-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Neighborhood Save Our Homes: Harriet Putterman (086-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - New York State Tenants Coalition: Michael Ehrmann (087-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - New York State Tenants Coalition: Mike McKee (087-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - New York State Tenants Coalition: Jim Garst (087-03), undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Northwest Bronx Community Organizing Project: Paul Brandt, S.J. (088-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Northwest Bronx Community Organizing Project: Jim Mitchell (088-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Ocean-Hill Brownsville Tenants Association: Father Powis (089-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Ocean-Kings Tenants Organization: Soloman Suartz (090-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Ocean-Kings Tenants Association: Norman Davis (090-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - 111th Street Block Association: Louise Garcia (091-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Operation Need: Mr. Rodney Pearsall (092-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Operation Need: George La Court (092-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Operation Open City: Barbara Parker (093-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Park Slope Neighborhood Tenants Council: Dorothy Rubin (094-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Park Slope Neighborhood Tenants Council: M. Shulman (094-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Park West Village Tenants Association: Maggie Payton (095-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Parkchester Tenants Association: Victor Zucher (096-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Polo Grounds Community Association: Mrs. O. Boulding (097-01), undated (Box 7, Folder data_value_missing_e0944f5c0a70b2bd3c8bdffd1917a1eb, Folder 63)
  - Polo Grounds Community Association: Israel Hicks (097-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Project Find for the Elderly: Elizabeth Trebony (098-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Project Find: Tim Wintermute (098-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Prospect Lefferts Gardens Neighborhood Association: Ms. Epstein (099-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Pueblo Nuevo: Lisa Kaplan (100-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Pueblo Nuevo: Kate Crampton (100-02), undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Quali-Cap (Queensbridge, Astoria, etc): Dolores Dwyer (102-01), undated (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Research Files (box 8): Leadership Questionnaires: Neighborhood Organizations
  - Queens Presidents Council: Marco Colos (103-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Queens Presidents Council: Paul Wolfe (103-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Queens Tenants Federation: Frank Lusk (104-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association: Hal Sobolov (107-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Riverdale Park Tenants Association: Walter Tolub (107-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association: Leah Williams (108-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Riverside Edgecombe Neighborhood Association: Jessica Barr (108-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - St. Nicholas Park Community Council: Theodore Anderson (109-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - St. Nicholas Park Community Council: June Gunn (109-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Service Association of East Harlem T's (part of Community Association of East Harlem Triangle): Alice Karnegay (110-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 7A Association: Barnard Haaft (111-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Sheepshead-Brighton Tenant Association: Vic Barron (112-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Simpson Street Development Association (SISDA): Barbara Boyd (113-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Simpson Street Development Association (SISDA): Sister Tom Collins (113-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - South Bronx Action Group: Santos Rivera (114-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - South Bronx Legal Services: Susan Kunstler (115-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - South Bronx Legal Services: Levine (116-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Southside Mission: Mr. Seisse (116-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - S. T. R. E. S. S.: Ms. Lemon (117-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - South Fordham Organization: Bill Frey (118-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - South Fordham Organization: Fr. Martin Miller (118-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Stuyvesant Town Tenant Association: Charles Lyman (119-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Tenants Power for Queens: Adele Bender (120-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Tower West: Sandy Edlestein (141-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Tremont Improvement Project: Susan Boyd (121-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Tremont Improvement Project: George Mazin (121-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Trinity Avenue Block Association: Mark Coleman (122-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Trinity Avenue Block Association: Mrs. Dixon (122-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Tudor City: John McKean (124-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Two Bridges Neighborhood Council: Sal Lodico (123-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - United Block Association: Leroy Walker (126-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - United Leadership Alliances (or United Leadership of 98th Street): Ms. Dasher (127-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - United Riverdale Tenants Association: Len Miller (128-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - University Heights Neighborhood Improvement: Father McNally (129-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - UPACA: Mrs. Mary Iemma (130-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - UPACA: Mrs. Jenkins (130-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board: Don Turner (131-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Urban Homesteading Assistance Board: Philip St. George (131-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - West Harlem Community Organization: Mrs. Pikes (132-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - West Harlem Community Organization: Margaret McNeil (132-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - West Harlem Group Assistance Inc: Tom Cunningham (133-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - West Harlem Group Assistance Inc: Virginia Thomas (133-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - West Side Tenants Union: Nancy Kyriacov (134-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - West Side Tenants Union: Bertha Hellman (134-02), undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - West Side Tenants Union: Michael Ehrmann (134-03), undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Williamburg Community Corp.: Carlos Lituinhook (135-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Williamburg Community Corp. Center 2: Mrs. Marrero (136-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Williamburg Community Corp. Center 6: Angelita Baez (137-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Windsor Park: Mark Weiss (138-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - West Bronx Jewish Community Council: Eileen Pental (142-01), undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - 1468 Fifth Avenue: Annette Dow, Mrs. Wimbush, Aug 14, 19xx (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - 8 West 119th Street: Carrie Williamson, Apr 16, 1976, Aug 14, 19xx [1975] (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - University Heights: Mrs. Kitty Di Casimirro, Mrs Pekla (129-06), Apr 6, 1976, May 22, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - University Heights: Joe Mascott(129-07), Dec 11, 1974-Apr 9, 1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - 2412 University Avenue: Mr. John Watson (129), Apr 26, 19xx, May 9, 19xx, undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - West Side Tenants Union: Angela Romano (134-06), July 17, 1975, June 28, 1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Research Files (box 9): Tenant Association Building Leader Questionnaires
  - Notecards from Interview, Folder #32, undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Adopt-A-Building: 212 Forsythe Street Tenant Organization: Marie Lawrence, Maralyn Thompson, July 21, 1975, Apr 12, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers: Chuck Laven, Mar 11, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - (Brooklyn Tenants Union): 143-137 Tenant Organization: 137 Sterling Street: Ms. May White (Building Leader), Ms Harder, Cain Hampton, May 24, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - (Brooklyn Tenants Union): 580 - Tenant Council: 580 Empire Boulevard: Elnora Seabrook, Sandra Brown, Aug 8, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Brighton Beach Tenant Association: 417 Brightwater Court: Mr. Dave Weinzweig, Aug 15, 19xx, Apr 5, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - (A.C.T.): Indiana Tenants Association: 67-25 Dartmouth Street, Forest Hills, NY: Mr. Robert Wolf, Ms. Laura Reich (President), July 17, 1975, Apr 1, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - (Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corp.) 959 Tenants Improvement Association: 959 St. Marks: Cassietta Bailey, Francis Dorsey, Renee Cobbs, July 16, 1975, Apr 12, 1976 undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Essex Tenants Association Council: 111-15 75th Avenue, Forest Hills, NY: Arthur A. Krieger, Louis Marcus, Aug 5, 1975, Mar 30, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - (Adopt-A-Building): 208-210 Forsythe Street Tenants Association: 210 Forsythe Street: Emily San Clemente, Kip Peticolas, July 30, 1975, Apr 22, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - (Adopt-A-Building): 517 East 11th Street Tenants Association: 517 East 11th Street: Dot Shari, July 14, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Adopt-A-Building: 188 East 3rd Street Organization: Penny Huntsboger, Renaldo Crespo, Oct 18, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Tenants Union: Margaret Cobbs, Mar 25, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - (Brownsville C.C.): 1920 Union Street: Mary Nesmith, Mar 31, 1976-May 5, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Chelsea Action Center: 265 West 19th Street Tenant Organization: Nelson De Jesus, Fernando Gongora, Aug 20, 1975, May 4, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Washington Heights Citizen Committee: 720 West 170th Street: Augusta Weinberger, Morton Orentlicher, Jun 14, 1975, Aug 1975, Apr 25, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Citizens Committee of Washington Heights: 621 West 169th Street: Tom Pedeschi, Aug 8, 1975, Jun 21, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - (Citizens Committee of Washington Heights and R.E.N.A): 235 Fort Washington Avenue: Eugenia Bernall, Irene Ginsburg, Aug 6, 19xx, Apr 7, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - City-Wide Anti-Poverty Committee on Housing: Sarah Farley (Vice Chairperson): pretest, Feb 13, 19xx, Feb 25, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Columbia Tenants Union: Ruth Indeck, Mar 18, 19xx (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Columbia Tenants Union: La Salle Tenants Association: 126 La Salle Street: Yolanda Calderon, Mr. Wong, Jul 29, 19xx, Apr 10, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - (Columbia Tenants Union): 215 West 101st Street Tenant Organization: 215 West 101st Street, NY: Bill Rowan, Jun 30, 1975-Apr 20, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Cooper Square Community Devlp: 7 East 3rd Street: Chuck Richie, Apr 29, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Crotona Tenants Coalition: 785 East 181st Street, Bronx: Joan Butler, Sister Patricia Dillon, Apr 15, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Crotona Tenants Council: 2120 Mapes Avenue, Bronx: Marie Alequin, Benedicta Ramos, July 15, 1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - 150 East 49th Street Tenant Group: 150 East 49th Street: Jacqueline Wein, Sep 1975, Apr 7, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - (Eldridge Street): 275 Broome Street Tenants Association: 275 Broome Street: Felix Rivera, Elba Torres, Jul 27, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Flatbush Tenants Council: 441 Ocean Avenue, Brooklyn: Marge Grudzinski, Jun 24, 1975, Apr 15, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Flatbush Tenants Association: 602-618 Ocean Parkway, Brooklyn: Mrs. Florence Birkenhead, May 8, 1975, May 10, 1976, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Research Files (box 10): Tenant Association Building Leader Questionnaires
  - (Flatbush Tenants Council): 1641 Ocean Avenue Tenants Association: 1641 Ocean Avenue, Brooklyn: Jennie Phillips, Oct 10, 1975, Apr 22, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Flatbush Tenants Council: 2744 Bedford Avenue, Brooklyn: Mrs. Newfield, Mrs. Fields, Apr 12, 1976, July 30, 19xx, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Flatbush Tenants Council: 1270 East 18th Street, Brooklyn: Tucks, Minnilli, Goldberg, Mr. Max Grossman, May 8, 1975, Jun 3, 1975, Apr 7, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Housing Conservation Coordinators: 695, 400, and 402 Tenants Association: 400 West 48 Street: Ralph Irezarry; HCC: Tenants Association Inc.: 695, 400, and 402 Tenants Association: Juanita Abreu, Jul 11, 1975, Apr 7, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chelsea Court Tower Tenants Association: 365 West 20th Street: Larry Malloy, Margot Howd, Jul 16, 1975, Jun 16, 19xx, Apr 12, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - (Hudson Guild Service Center): 250 West 24th Street/255 West 23rd Street/255 West 24th Street: Dave Shear, Jun 18, 1975, Apr 7, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 570 Erdy 204th Street Association: 570 West 204th Street: Millie Adaire, Aug 12, [1975], Apr 9, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 3034 Albany Crescent Tenant Association: 3034 Albany Crescent, Bronx: Ann Davitt, Peggy McMahon, Dec 2, 1975, Apr 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - (Longwood Community Management): Belmont Tenants Association: 212 Belmont Avenue, Bronx: Clifford Hinton, Mrs. Jones, July 1975, May 7, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Los Sures: Kathy Berry, Mar 13, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - (Los Sures): 227 South 2nd Street, Brooklyn: Mr. Santiago, Isibro Carlos, Mr. and Mrs. Bagu, Apr 17, 1976, Apr 24, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - South Side Organization/Los Sures: 225 South 3rd Street, Brooklyn: Luis Domenech, Julio Diaz, Apr 10, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Marble Kingsbridge Futures Association: 232nd Street Tenant Association: 225 West 232nd Street, Bronx: Anne Blake, Paul Kahane (Vice-President), Aug 4, [1975], Apr 21, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Melrose Organization: 1356 University Avenue, Bronx: Mr. Meyreles, Apr 4, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Met Council Bay Ridge Branch: 145 95th Street: Joan O'Brien, Theresa Kelly, Jun 16, 1975, Apr [1976], undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - (Met Council Bay Ridge Branch): 7101 Colonial Road, Brooklyn: Robert Gambale, Joe Redici, Aug 5, 1975, Apr 16, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - (Met Council West Side Branch): 3681 Broadway: Mrs. Ghigliotti, Maria Sato, Jul 28, 1975, Apr 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - (Met Council Crown Heights Branch): 1114 New York Avenue Tenants Association: 1114 New York Avenue, Brooklyn: Patrick Sullivan, Janet Washington, Aug 6, 1975, Apr 7, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - (Met Council Harlem Branch): 312 East 91st Street Tenant Organization: 312 East 91st Street, NY: Joyce Wackenhut, I. Luhn, Apr 25, 19xx, May 15, 1975, May 22, 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - 1644 Amsterdam Avenue: Leroy Oliver, Mrs. Cora A. Williams, May 15, 1975, May 22, 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Concerned Cooperators: 35 Montgomery: Anna Watson, May 6, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Fairfield Towers Tenants Association: 12205 Flatlands Avenue, Brooklyn: Susan Hoffman, Amelia Roberts, May 2, 1975, Apr 15, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - (Met Council): Promenade Tenant Association: 150 West 225th Street, Bronx: Mr. Edwin C. Hutching, Jr., Henrietta McAlister, Mar 27, 1975-Apr 15, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - A.C.T. and Met Council: (Rutledge Tenant Organization): 89-18 Rutledge Avenue, Rego Park, Queens: Don Speary, Mrs. Carol White, Aug 20, 1975, Apr 14, 1976, undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Research Files (box 11): Tenant Association Building Leader Questionnaires
  - (Met Council Lower East Side Branch): 92 Perry Street: Susan Wilson (leader), Iris Olshin (chairperson); Student Paper: Met Council, May 6, 1975, May 21, 1975, Apr 13, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Small Committee of Five Tenants: 157 First Avenue: Steven Fisher, Trish Cameron, May 9, 19xx, May 11, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - (Met Council): 159 Christopher Street Tenants Union: 159 Christopher Street: John Stanley, Eileen Crianza, Jul 29, 1975, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 157 West 105th Street, NY: Juanita Nesbit; 20 West 86th Street: Cobham; 50 West 106th Street Tenants Association: Leonard Lerner: Fieldwork Report, Apr 2, 1975-May 2, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Met Council on Housing: 302 Convent Avenue: Curtis Trueheart, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - (Met Council): 211 West 106th Street Tenant Organization: 211 West 106th Street/875 West End Avenue, NY: Ken Rentro c/o Arnold Fay, Apr 18, 1975-Apr 27, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - WAS: 230 Park Place, Brooklyn: Samuel Weiner, Apr 23, 1975, May 18, 1975, Apr 14, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Concerned Co-op: 25 Montgomery Street, NY: Kate Winters, Louis Schloss, May 14, 1975, Apr 27, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - C.A.R.I.: 2075 Second Avenue: Augusta Carlson, May 15, 1975, Jun 19, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Fairfield Towers Tenant Association, Apr 26, 1975, May 2, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Central Park Gardens T's Association: 50 West 97th Street, NY, Ivan Merber, Ruth Ellin, Oct 24, 1975, Jun 21, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - (Morris Heights Neighborhood Association): 1821 Unversity Avenue Tenants Association: 1821 University, Bronx: Rafael Lopez, Miriam Rodriguez, July 15 [1975]-Apr 10, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - (Mosholu Woodlawn Association): 3464 Knox Place Tenants Association: 3464 Knox Place, Bronx: Kay Collins, Dominic Nicholson, Jul 16, 1975-Apr 21, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - (Mosholu Woodlawn Association): 3291 Hull Avenue, Bronx: Mrs Geng, Francine Zimmer, Jun 17, 19xx, Jul 17, [1975], Apr 21, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - New York State Tenants Coalition: Russell Anne Nobles, Mar 13, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Ocean Hill Brownsville Tenants Association: 2170 Atlantic Avenue, Brooklyn: Grant Purdy, Mabel Mosley, Sep 2, 1975, Dec 16, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ocean-Kings Tenants Association: 1860 East 12th Street: Norma Tirino, Metzer, Goldford, Adelming, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - (Parkslope Tenants Council): 64 7th Avenue Tenants Association: 64 7th Avenue, Brooklyn: Tomisina Stith, Audrey Wilson, June 17, 1975-May 3, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Polo Grounds: 145 West 127th Street: Lela Williams, Aug 2, 19xx, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - (Project Find): The Hotel St. James Tenant Association: Hotel St. James, 109 West 45th Street: Lora Edler, Jun 30, 1975, Apr 13, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - (Project Find): Knickerbocker Tenant's Association: Hotel Knickerbocker, 120 West 45th Street: Mary Ruff, Ethel Hurtt, July 3, 1975, Jul 24, 1975, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Prospect-Lefferts Garden Neighborhood Association: 170 Hawthawn Street, Brooklyn: Betty Frumpkin, Pat Roberts, July 24, 1975-Apr 10, [1976], undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - (Pueblo Nuevo): 72 Clinton Street Housing Dev. Fund Corp.: 72 Clinton Street: Gloria Manigo, undated (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - (Queens President's Council): Hanford Tenant Organization: 65-38 Booth Street, Rego Park, Queens: John Mascerino, Maurice Seide, Jul 1, 1975, Apr 9, 1976, undated (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Shellball Tenants Association: 83-00 Talbot Street, Kew Gardens, Queens: Mike Jacobs, Joan Gampert, Apr 1975-Apr 24, [1976], undated (Box 11, Folder 25)